California ephemera collection, 1860-
California Ephemera Collection,
- Getty Center. Los Angeles, California (Boxes 234, 280)
  Box 234 - 4 folders.
- Getty Conservation Institute. Marina Del Rey, California (Box 220)
- Getty Research Institute. Santa Monica, California (Box 220)
- Getty Villa. Malibu, California (Box 280)
- Gewelt, W. K. (Box 32)
- Ghirardelli Chocolate. San Francisco. (Box 195)
- Giannini, Amadeo Peter, 1870 - 1949 (Box 32)
- Gildzen, Alex (Box 266)
- Gill, Irving, 1870 - 1936 (Box 186)
- Gillett, James Norris, 1860 - (Box 32)
- Gilman Historic Ranch and Museum. Banning, California (Box 238)
- Gilman, Charlotte (Perkins) Stetson, 1860 - 1935 (Box 32)
- Gilmore Stadium. Los Angeles. (Box 32)
- Gilroy, California (Box 266)
- Giulii, Nicalo (Box 32)
- Gladding, McBean & Co. (Box 32)
- Glauer, J.B., major (Box 32)
- Glendale, California (Box 32)
- Glendale, California - Business cards and promotional material (Box 209)
- Glendale, California - Restaurants, lunchrooms, etc. (Boxes 188, 280)
- Glendale, California - Tract maps (Box 209)
- Glendora, California (Box 33)
- Glenn County, California (Box 33)
- Golden Globe Awards (Box 266)
- Golden State Museum. Sacramento, California (Box 238)
- Golf (Box 266)
- Golf - Miniature (Box 220)
- Granice, Harry H., d. 1915 (Box 33)
- Grant, Ulysses Simpson, 1852 - 1929 (Box 33)
- Grass Valley, California (Box 33)
- Greater Los Angeles Zoo Association (Boxes 33, 225)
  See shelf list for cross references.
  Box 225 is an oversize box.
- Greek Letter Societies (Box 33)
- Greek-Americans - California (Box 209)
- Green Party (Boxes 225, 238)
- Green, Edwin, 1913 - 1966 (Box 33)
- Green, Will Semple, 1832 - 1905 (Box 33)
- Greyhound Bus Co. (Box 251)
  Bus schedules, ca. 1942.
- Griffes, James Hartness, 1863 - (Box 33)
- Griffith Observatory. Los Angeles. (Box 155)
- Griffith, Beatrice Winston, - 1976 (Box 155)
  X. Thompson, Beatrice Winston Griffith, - 1976
- Griffith, Griffith Jenkins, 1852 - 1919 (Box 155)
  1. Griffith, Mrs. Mary A.C., 1864? - 1948
- Gronk (Box 253)
  SEE: La Vida Nueva
- Gross - Pacific Sanger - Bundes. Los Angeles. (Box 255)
- Gross, Julius W., 1846? - 1940 (Box 33)
- Guerneville, California (Box 238)
- Gwin, William McKendree, 1805 - 1903 (Box 33)
- Gymnastics (Box 220)
- Gypsy Boots (Box 191)
- Hagunin, James Richard (Box 38)
- Hahn, Jim (Box 266)
- Haight, Henry Huntley, 1825 - 1878 (Box 33)
- Haines, William (Box 238)
- Hale, George Ellery, 1868 - 1938 (Box 33)
- Half Moon Bay, California (Boxes 188, 280)
- Hall, Manly Palmer, 1901 - (Box 33)
- Halleck, Henry Wager, 1815 - 1872 (Box 34)
- Hamilton, Peggy (Box 209)
- Hanna, Phil Townsend, 1896 - (Box 34)
- Harbors - California (Box 34)
  X. California - harbors.
- Harbors - California, Southern (Box 34)
- Hard Times. Los Angeles, California (Box 213)
- Hare Krishna Cultural Center. Los Angeles, California (Box 266)
- Harman, Jane (Box 266)
- Harper, Arthur C., 1866 - 1948? (Box 34)
- Hart, William Surrey, 1870 - 1946 (Box 199)
- Harte, Francis Bret, 1836 - 1902 (Box 34)
- Hastings, Serranus Clinton, 1814 - 1893 (Box 34)
- Hawes, Horace (Box 34)
- Hayakawa, Samuel Ichiye, 1906 - (Box 34)
- Hayes, Everis Anson, 1855 -1942 (Box 34)
- Hayfork, California (Box 34)
- Haynes, John Randolph, 1853 - 1934 (Box 34)
- Hayward, California (Alameda County) (Box 34)
- Hazardous Waste disposal - California (Box 266)
- Heal the Bay. Santa Monica, California (Boxes 209, 266)
- Healdsburg, California (Box 238)
- Healey, Dorothy, 1914 - (Box 34)
- Health Care (Box 238)
- Health Education - California (Box 34)
- Health Maintenance Organizations - California (Box 220)
- Health Resorts, Watering Places, etc. - California (Box 34)
- Hearst - San Simeon State Historical Monument (Box 156)
- Hearst, George, 1820 - 1891 (Box 34)
- Hearst, Patricia Campbell, 1954 - (Box 225)
- Hearst, Phoebe A. (Box 209)
- Hearst, William Randolph, 1863 - 1951 (Box 156)
- Heineman, Theodore William, 1836 - (Box 34)
- Hemet, California (Boxes 34, 251)
  - Ramona pageant brochure., 1935.; Item No. 1 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    Promotional brochure for Hemet's annual outdoor dramatic production of Helen Hunt Jackson's historical romance, Ramona.
  - Ramona pageant 13th annual presentation brochure., 1936.; Item No. 2 (Box 34, Folder 2)
- Heney, Francis Joseph, 1859 - 1937 (Box 34)
- Henry E. Huntington Library and Art Gallery. San Marino, California (Boxes 125, 126, 127, 255, 266)
  1. Libraries - California. Box 127 - 5 folders.
- Hermosa Beach, California (Boxes 34, 280)
- Herpetology (Box 238)
- Hesperia, California (Box 266)
- Hetch Hetchy Valley, California (Box 156)
- Highland Park (Los Angeles, California) (Box 220)
- Highway 395.
  SEE California - Description and travel - Route 395.
- Highway Planning - California - Los Angeles County (Box 35)
- Highway Safety - California (Box 35)
- Hilgard, Eugene Woldemar, 1833 - 1916 (Box 35)
- Hinkley, California (Box 266)
- Hip Hop (Box 266)
- Historical Markers - California (Box 35)
- Historical Markers - Los Angeles County, California (Box 35)
  1. Los Angeles County, Calif. - history
- Historical Markers - Placer County, California (Box 35)
- Historical Society of Southern California. Los Angeles. (Box 35)
- Historical Society of Southern California. Newsletter. (Box 35)
- Hittell, John Shertzer, 1825 - 1901 (Box 35)
- Hittell, Theodore Henry, 1830 - 1917 (Box 35)
- Holden, Nate (Box 186)
- Holden, Stanley (Box 266)
- Holder, Charles Frederick, 1851 - 1915 (Box 35)
- Holistic Health (Box 280)
- Hollister, California (Box 35)
- Hollywood Bowl (Boxes 37, 199, 220)
  Box 220 - 2 folders.
- Hollywood Humanist Society (Box 37)
- Hollywood Independent Citizens Committee of the Arts, Sciences and Professions (Box 37)
- Hollywood, California (Boxes 36, 186, 199, 238)
- Hollywood, California - Description and travel (Boxes 266, 280)
- Hollywood, California - Florentine Gardens (Box 266)
- Hollywood, California - Hotels, taverns, etc. (Boxes 209, 251)
- Holmes, Burton, 1870 - 1957 (Box 156)
  1. Holmes, Burton, 1970 - 1957 - Portrait. 2. Photographers - California - Southern.
- Home Furnishings (Box 280)
- Home Repairs (Box 280)
- Horse Racing - California (Box 156)
- Horticultural Exhibitions - California (Box 263)
  Cotton scarf for San Francisco Landscape Garden Show, no date.
- Horticulture - California (Box 188)
- Horticulture - California - Societies (Box 238)
- Hospitals - California, southern (Boxes 157, 188)
- Hot Springs - California (Box 220)
- Hotels, taverns, etc. - California (Box 157)
- Houseman, John, 1902 - (Box 38)
- Houser, Frederick W., 1871 - 1942 (Box 38)
- Housing - California (Boxes 38, 209, 213)
- How, James Eads, 1868 - (Box 38)
- Howard, Burt Estes, 1862 - 1913 (Box 38)
- Howard, Frederick H., 1875 - 1948 (Box 38)
- Howie Mouse. Pacific Palisades, California (Box 190)
- Howlett, John Thomas, 1949 - 1991 (Box 209)
- Hughes, Langston, 1902 - 1967 (Box 188)
- Humboldt County, California (Box 157)
- Hunt, Rockwell Dennis, 1868 - (Box 38)
- Huntington Beach, California (Boxes 38, 188)
- Huntington Hartford Foundation. Santa Monica. (Box 38)
- Huntington Lake, California (Box 38)
- Huntington Park, California (Box 196)
- Huntington, Collis Potter, 1821 - 1900 (Box 38)
- Huntington, Mrs. Arabella (Yarrington), ca. 1850 - 1924 (Box 38)
- Hussey, William Joseph, 1862 - 1926 (Box 38)
- Ice skating (Box 238)
- Ichioka, Yuji. 1936-2002 (Box 267)
- Identity Theft - California (Box 280)
- Idyllwild, California (Box 38)
- Iles, Harry, 1852 - 1948 (Box 38)
- Imperial County, California (Box 158)
- Independence, California (Box 267)
- Independent Progressive Party (Box 188)
- Indian Wells, California (Box 238)
- Indians of North America - California (Box 39)
- Indio, California (Box 158)
- Industry - History - California (Box 39)
- Inglewood, California (Boxes 40, 213)
- Inglewood, California Crenshaw Christian Church. (Box 40)
- Inland Empire (California) (Box 280)
- Insect control (Box 280)
- Institute for Studies of Destructive Behaviors and the Suicide Prevention Center (Box 40)
  X. Suicide Prevention Center.
- Institute of Mentalphysics. Los Angeles, California (Boxes 188, 267)
- Insurance Companies (Box 220)
- Insurance, Life - California - Los Angeles (Box 40)
- Interior Design (Box 238)
- International College. Los Angeles. (Box 40)
- International Gay and Lesbian Archives. Hollywood, California (Boxes 195, 280)
- International Longshoremen's Association. Long Beach, California (Box 195)
- International Settlement. Los Angeles. (Box 40)
- International Society for General Semantics. Los Angeles Chapter. (Box 40)
- Internet (Box 238)
- Interrace Magazine. Beverly Hills, California (Box 238)
- Interurban Press. Glendale, California (Box 40)
- Inyo County, California (Box 158)
  1. Eastern California Museum, Independence, Calif. 2. Mono County, Calif.
- Inyo Register and Owens Valley Herald. (Box 253)
  Supplement No. 1. 7 Jan. 1925.
  Cross reference: Owens Valley, Calif.
- Iranian-Americans - California - Directories (Box 256)
  .
- Iranian-Americans - California - Orange County - Directories (Box 216)
- Iranian-Americans in California (Box 238)
- Irish, John Powell, 1843 - 1923 (Box 40)
- Irvine Ranch, California (Boxes 158, 280)
- Irvine, California (Box 238)
- Irving, William (Box 40)
- Irwin, William, 1827 - 1889 (Box 40)
- Isherwood, Christopher (Box 280)
- Islam - California (Box 238)
- Italians in California (Box 40)
- J. Paul Getty Museum (Box 187)
- J.W. Robinson Co. (Box 40)
- Jackson, California (Box 40)
- Jackson, Donald L. (Box 40)
  The Washington Letter, 1955
- Jackson, Helen Maria (Fiske) Hunt, 1831 - 1885 (Box 40)
- Jackson, Michael (Box 281)
- James, George Wharton, 1858 - 1923 (Box 40)
- Jamestown, California (Box 238)
- Japanese American Cultural and Community Center. Los Angeles, California (Box 188)
- Japanese American National Museum (Los Angeles, California) (Boxes 210, 267)
  Box 210 - 2 folders. Box 267 - 2 folders.
- Japanese in California (Boxes 41, 42, 254)
  Crossroads, the Los Angeles Nisei Weekly.
  Vol. 1, no. 1 (May 28, 1948), vol. 1, no. 3 (June 11, 1948), vol. 1, no. 18 (Sept. 24, 1948). Box 254 = oversize flat box, 15" x 19."
  - 70,000 American refugees: made in the U.S.A.., ca. 1943.; Item No. 1 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Education section summary: report to Ralph P. Meritt and his general staff meeting., May 31, 1945.; Item No. 2 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    Summary of the elementary, secondary, and adult education programs put into place at the Manzanar War Relocation Camp for evacuated Japanese Americans.
  - Crossroads (Los Angeles, Calif.)., May 28, 1948-.; Item No. 1 (Folder 1)
    "The Los Angeles Nisei Weekly" "10 cents a copy"
- Japanese in California - Pre World War II. (Box 41)
  1) Pre-World War II. 2-3) World War II and after.
  - The Japanese in California: comments in the California press., 1920.; Item No. 1 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - What we're fighting for: statements by United States servicemen about Americans of Japanese descent., ca. 1944.; Item No. 1 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Assembly bill no. 78: an act to regulate the ownership or possession of land by aliens., January 8, 1909.; Item No. 2 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - The displaced Japanese-Americans., 1944.; Item No. 2 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - An appeal to justice: the injustice of the proposed initiative measure., 1920.; Item No. 3 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Campaign Committee of Asiatic Exclusion League of California., August 9, 1910.; Item No. 4 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    Flier formatted as an open letter, to call attention to the legislative records of two California assemblymen.
  - Men and women! Protect your homes from loathsome Oriental diseases!., ca. 1910.; Item No. 5 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Our Japanese question., ca. 1910.; Item No. 6 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - White or Jap: which?., 1908.; Item No. 7 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Anti-Jap Laundry League report for 1911., January 11, 1912.; Item No. 8 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Will the Japanese predominate?., June 1909.; Item No. 9 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Does the savings justify the risk?., ca. 1910.; Item No. 10 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Check the Japanese industrial invasion., January 1912.; Item No. 11 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Jap-laundry patrons: attention!., ca. 1910.; Item No. 12 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - In the interest of peace with Japan patronize white industries only., June 1913.; Item No. 13 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Can we count on you?., 1908.; Item No. 14 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Facts in the case: a statement based upon the report of the State Board of Control., ca. 1920.; Item No. 15 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Assembly bill no. 14: an act to amend section 1662 of the political code., January 8, 1909.; Item No. 16 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Los Angeles Farmer's Supply Company catalog., undated.; Item No. 17 (Box 41, Folder 1)
- Jay, Ricky (Box 220)
- Jazz Musicians. Los Angeles, California (Box 267)
- Jeffers, Robinson, 1887 - 1962 (Box 40)
- Jenner, California (Box 267)
- Jewelry making (Box 251)
- Jewett, Elizabeth Stuart (Box 43)
- Jewett, Patty Stuart (Box 43)
- Jews - California - Los Angeles - directories (Box 216)
- Jews in California (Boxes 43, 44, 199)
- Job training - California - Los Angeles (Box 238)
- Johnson, Earvin Magic (Box 281)
- Johnson, George P., 1885 - 1977 (Box 210)
- Johnson, Hiram Warren, 1866 - 1945 (Box 159)
- Johnson, John Neely, - 1872 (Box 159)
- Joint Amendment Campaign Committee. San Francisco. (Box 159)
- Jones, A. Quincy (Box 267)
- Jones, Idwal, 1890 - (Box 159)
- Jones, Mattison B., 1869? - 1941 (Box 159)
- Jordan, David Starr, 1851 - 1932 (Box 159)
- Jordan, Frank C., 1860 -1940 (Box 159)
- Joshua Journal. Joshua Tree, California (Box 190)
  Box 190 is oversize flat box.
- Joshua Tree National Park (California) (Box 238)
- Julian, California (Box 159)
- June Lake, California (Box 220)
- Kabbalah Centre. Los Angeles, California (Box 238)
- Kahn, Julius, 1861 - 1924 (Box 159)
- KCET - T.V. Los Angeles, California (Boxes 238, 253)
- Kearney Park. Fresno, California (Box 159)
  1. Fresno, Calif. 2. Kearney, Theodore.
- Keeler, James Edward, 1857 - 1900 (Box 159)
- Kefauver, Estes (Box 191)
- Keller, Matthew, d. 1881 (Box 159)
  X. Keller, Mateo.
- Kelseyville, California (Box 281)
- Kenny, Robert Walker, 1901 - (Box 159)
  l. Kenny, Robert Walerk, 1901 - - Portrait.
- Kent, William H.B., 1878 - (Box 159)
- Kent, William, 1864 - 1928 (Box 159)
- Kerckhoff, William George, 1856 - 1929 (Box 159)
- Kern County, California (Box 45)
- Kern County, California - airports (Box 188)
- Kernville, California (Box 45)
- Ketchum, Robert Glenn, 1847 - (Box 45)
- Killingsworth, Edward (Box 267)
- King, Clarence, 1842 - 1901 (Box 45)
- King, Thomas Starr, 1824 - 1863 (Box 45)
- Kings Canyon National Park, California (Box 45)
- Kings County, California (Box 45)
- Kinney, Abbot, 1850 - 1920 (Box 45)
- Kip, William Ingraham, bp., 1811 - 1893 (Box 45)
- Kitaj, R.B. (Box 281)
- Knight, George Alexander, 1851 - 1916 (Box 45)
- Knight, Virginia Frances (Piergue), 1918 - (Box 45)
- Knight, William Henry, 1835 - 1925 (Box 46)
- Knott, Walter, 1889 - (Box 46)
- Knott's Berry Farm. Buena Park, California (Box 191)
- Knowland, Joseph Russell, 1873 - (Box 46)
- Knowland, William Fife, 1908 - (Box 46)
- Koepfli, Joseph O., 1865? - 1942 (Box 46)
- Kovacs, Ernie, 1919 - 1962 (Box 46)
  1. Kovacs, Ernie, 1919 - 1962 - Portrait. 2. Adams, Edie, 1929 - Portrait.
- Krehbiel, Edward Benjamin, 1878 - (Box 46)
- Krisiloff, Flora Gil (Box 267)
- La Canada, California (Box 46)
- La Fiesta de Los Angeles (Boxes 192, 261)
  - Southern Californian., September 25, 1931.; Item No. 1 (Box 192, Folder 1)
- La Grange, O.H. (Box 46)
- La Habra, California (Box 281)
- La Jolla, California (Box 46)
- La Mesa, California (Box 46)
- La Quinta, California (Box 267)
- La Verne, California (Box 239)
- La Vida Nueva (Box 253)
  1:1 (26 Feb. 1969), 1:6 (11 May 1969), 2:1 (5 Dec. 1969), 3:2 (29 Apr. 1970).
  Cross reference: Gronk.
- La Vida Nueva. Los Angeles, Calif. (Box 253)
  Feb. 26, 1969; May 14, 1969; Dec. 5, 1969; Apr. 29, 1970.
- Labor and laboring classes - California (Boxes 46, 160)
  Box 160 - 3 folders.
  - Boycott scab products!., ca. 1973.; Item No. 1 (Box 160, Folder 1)
  - Celebrate the International Labor Holiday., May 1, 1935.; Item No. 2 (Box 160, Folder 1)
  - Don't mess it up now, buddy! Be sure that home-front jobs are open to ALL Americans!., ca. 1945(?).; Item No. 3 (Box 160, Folder 1)
- Laguna Beach, California (Boxes 46, 190, 239, 281)
- Laguna Beach, California - Business cards and promotional material (Box 210)
- Laguna, California (Box 214)
- Lake Arrowhead (Boxes 97, 239, 262, 267)
  See also: Arrowhead, Lake (old entry)
  Box 262 is an oversize flat box, 22-1/2" x 28-1/2".
- Lake County, California (Box 46)
- Lake Nacimiento, California (Box 239)
- Lake Norconian, California (Box 281)
- Lake Tahoe, California (Boxes 225, 239)
- Lancaster, California (Boxes 188, 281)
- Land Value Insurance - Los Angeles (Box 267)
- Land's End (Box 46)
- Langdon, William Henry, 1873 - 1939 (Box 46)
- Lankershim, California (Box 221)
- Larchmont Chronicle (Box 185)
- Larkin, Edgar Lucien, 1847 - 1924 (Box 46)
- Lassen County, California (Boxes 188, 281)
- Lassen Volcanic National Park, California (Box 46)
- Latham, Milton Slocum, 1827 - 1882 (Box 46)
- Lauck, Joseph B., 1846 - (Box 46)
- Laughton, Charles, 1899 - 1962 (Box 46)
  1. Laughton, Charles, 1899 - 1962 - Portrait. Lancaster, Elsa, 1902 - Portrait.
- Lautner, John. (Box 267)
- Lava Beds National Monument, California (Modoc County) (Box 46)
- Laventhal, Joseph, 1871? - 1942 (Box 46)
- Lawler, Oscar, 1875 - 1966 (Box 46)
- Lawlor, William Patrick, 1854 - (Box 46)
- Laws Railroad Museum. Laws, California (Box 188)
- Lawson, John Howard, 1895 - (Box 46)
  See shelf list for partial list of contents.
- Layne, Joseph Gregg, 1885 - 1952 (Boxes 47, 195)
- Laytonville, California (Box 239)
- League of Women Voters of California (Box 47)
- League of Women Voters of Los Angeles (Box 47)
- LeConte, Joseph, 1823 - 1901 (Box 47)
- Lee Vining, California (Box 267)
- Lee, John Baker, 1907 - 1961 (Box 47)
- Legoland. Carlsbad, California (Boxes 239, 281)
- Leimert Park, California (Box 221)
- Lempertz, Thomas Q., 1902 - 1980 (Box 47)
- LePrade, Ruth (Box 47)
- Levi-Strauss & Co. San Francisco. (Box 210)
- Liability for traffic accidents - California (Box 46)
- Liberace (Box 199)
- Libraries (Boxes 47, 160)
- Libraries - California State Library (Box 47)
- Libraries - California, Southern (Box 188)
- License plates (Box 221)
- Lichtenberger, Herman C., 1868 - 1941 (Box 47)
- Lick, James, 1796 - 1876 (Box 47)
- Liddecoat, Thomas H.W., 1864? - 1942 (Box 47)
- Lighthouses - California (Box 47)
- Lincoln Club. Los Angeles. (Box 47)
- Lipton, Lawrence, 1898 - (Box 47)
- Lissner, Meyer, 1871 - 1930 (Box 47)
- Livermore, California (Boxes 47, 281)
- Liverpool Shop. Los Angeles, California (Box 251)
- Locke, California (Box 267)
- Locke, Charles Edward, bp., 1858 - 1940 (Box 47)
- Loeb, Jacques, 1859 - 1924 (Box 47)
- Loleta, California (Box 239)
- Loma Linda, California (Box 187)
- Lompoc, California (Boxes 47, 192)
- London, Jack, 1876 - 1916 (Box 47)
- Lone Pine, California (Box 267)
- Long Beach Chautauqua Assembly (Box 48)
- Long Beach Symphony Orchestra (Box 281)
- Long Beach, California (Boxes 48, 199, 210, 214, 239, 251)
- Long Beach, California - Churches (Box 48)
- Long Beach, California - Queen Mary (Boxes 210, 267)
- Long Beach, California - Sports (Box 281)
- Los Adobes Art Gallery. Santa Barbara, California (Box 48)
- Los Altos, California (Box 267)
- Los Angeles Aqueduct (Box 48)
- Los Angeles Art Association (Box 160)
- Los Angeles Audubon Society (Box 267)
- Los Angeles Avengers (Football team) (Box 243)
- Los Angeles Book Club (Box 48)
- Los Angeles Center for Photographic Studies. Los Angeles, California (Box 17)
  Formerly filed under Center for Photographic Studies.
- Los Angeles Center of the American Academy of Political and Social Science (Box 61)
- Los Angeles Citizens' Committee to Support Labor's Rights (Box 61)
- Los Angeles City College. Los Angeles, California (Box 210)
- Los Angeles City Employee Association (Box 61)
- Los Angeles City Historical Society (Box 61)
- Los Angeles City Historical Society. Los Angeles, California (Box 221)
- Los Angeles Clippers (Baseketball team) (Box 243)
- Los Angeles Committees of Correspondence (Box 61)
- Los Angeles Community Concer Association (Box 61)
- Los Angeles Conservancy (Boxes 61, 281)
- Los Angeles Contemporary Exhibitions (LACE) (Box 282)
- Los Angeles County - Sheriff's Department (Box 267)
- Los Angeles County - Tract maps (Box 213)
- Los Angeles County Air Pollution Control District (Box 61)
  X. Los Angeles County, Calif. Air Pollution Control District.
- Los Angeles County Arboretum and Botanic Garden. Arcadia, California (Box 282)
- Los Angeles County Art Institute. Los Angeles. (Box 62)
- Los Angeles County Museum of Art (Boxes 63, 243, 282)
- Los Angeles County Museum of Natural History (Boxes 64, 282)
- Los Angeles County, California (Box 167)
- Los Angeles County, California Department of Mental Health. (Box 62)
- Los Angeles County, California Department of Public Social Service. (Box 62)
- Los Angeles County, California Department of Recreation, Camps and Playgrounds. (Box 186)
- Los Angeles County, California Department of Small Craft Harbors. (Box 62)
- Los Angeles County, California Fair. (Box 62)
- Los Angeles County, California Foster Care (Box 282)
- Los Angeles County, California Grand Jury. (Box 62)
- Los Angeles County, California Juvenile Hall (Box 62)
- Los Angeles County, California Planning Congress. (Box 62)
- Los Angeles County, California Politics and government (Box 62)
- Los Angeles County, California Public Library. (Box 63)
- Los Angeles County. Health Department. (Box 62)
- Los Angeles Daily News (Box 168)
- Los Angeles Dodgers (Baseball team) (Boxes 195, 243, 252)
  Box 252 is an oversize flat box, 21" x 25".
- Los Angeles Enterprise. Los Angeles, California (Box 251)
  1961 Apr 21.
- Los Angeles Examiner (Box 168)
- Los Angeles Family History Center. Los Angeles, California (Box 221)
- Los Angeles Friends of Tibet (Box 210)
- Los Angeles Galaxy (Soccer team) (Box 243)
- Los Angeles Gas and Electric Corp. (Box 192)
- Los Angeles Gay and Lesbian Center. Los Angeles, California (Box 267)
- Los Angeles Grand Opera Association (Box 168)
- Los Angeles Herald Examiner (Boxes 168, 252)
  Box 252 - Final edition, Thursday, November 1989. 2 copies.
- Los Angeles Historic Theatre Foundation (Box 221)
- Los Angeles Historical Society (Box 168)
- Los Angeles Institute of Contemporary Art (Box 168)
- Los Angeles International Airport (Boxes 203, 243)
  X. Airports - Los Angeles.
  Box 203 is an oversize poster box. See also: Los Angeles, Calif. - Department of Airports.
- Los Angeles International Film Exposition (Box 168)
- Los Angeles Kings (Hockey team) (Box 282)
- Los Angeles Lakers (Basketball team) (Box 282)
- Los Angeles Library Association (Box 168)
- Los Angeles Marathon (Box 267)
- Los Angeles Marathon. XVII (Box 268)
- Los Angeles Memorial Coliseum (Box 163)
- Los Angeles Microscopical Society (Box 65)
- Los Angeles Mirror, 1948 - 1962 (Box 65)
- Los Angeles Opera (Box 282)
- Los Angeles Philharmonic Orchestra (Boxes 65, 268)
- Los Angeles Physicians Art Society (Box 65)
- Los Angeles Postal News (Box 221)
- Los Angeles Public Library (Boxes 65, 282)
- Los Angeles Railway (Box 65)
- Los Angeles Region Goals Project (Box 168)
- Los Angeles Reporter. Los Angeles, California (Box 251)
  1965 Mar 24.
- Los Angeles Sparks (Basketball team) (Box 268)
- Los Angeles Star (Box 168)
  Photostat of vol. 1, no. 1, dated 17 May 1951.
- Los Angeles State and County Arboretum. Arcadia, California (Box 168)
  XX. Rancho Santa Anita. Los Angeles County, Calif.
- Los Angeles Steamship Company (Box 168)
- Los Angeles Stock Exchange (Box 168)